BEOMHA LOGISTICS
-Did you check this?
-Yeah.
That looks good.
You said it'd be suicide.
So why'd you come here?
Preparing to die means you'll live.
Otherwise, you'll surely die.
And as members of the society,
we're connected now, right?
So you planned that.
Talking to him the way that you did.
The guy needs tough love.
You know, he's the only hope we've got.
I'm on my way, Min-suk.
I promise I won't be late this time.
God, I hate superhumans.
I got a thousand won for each of you.
We'll be done here soon.
Kang Sang-ung.
He came down through the ceiling.
Your loser's here.
Yeah, I've got ears, you know.
I almost feel bad for you.
Considering you're all about to die.
Do what we planned.
Min-suk, you here?
Min-suk!
It's never easy.
Why would today be any different?
If they keep swarming in,
even a thousand won per person
won't be enough.
I thought you said
it was a suicide mission?
-How'd you get through everyone?
-Through the roof.
Powers are back?
Of course. He fell, like, five stories.
Ah.
Sang-ung! Kang Sang-ung!
Let go, damn it!
-Min-suk!
-Sang-ung!
Let go of me!
-Go on, Sang-ung.
-Be careful!
Save Min-suk and get that bastard!
Let go!
Handle these guys.
Sang-ung. Sang-ung! Kang Sang-ung!
Let me go!
Sang-ung!
There's a lot of them, Byeon.
Come up here!
Sang-ung.
What took you so long?
I've been busy.
Sorry.
Sang-ung! Kang Sang-ung!
No!
Hey! Hey!
Sang-ung, are you okay?
Are you crazy?
-I'm sorry.
-Sang-ung, are you okay?
I needed to make sure.
You're not healing.
So you're out of money, then.
Let's finish this quietly.
Don't do anything crazy.
Just give me your superpowers,
then I'll let you both leave here safely.
And if you don't…
…then your girl
takes an elevator ride.
Superpowers.
What's so great about 'em anyway?
Have you decided?
The wallet!
Byeon, can you hear me?
Mr. Attorney.
-Damn it.
-Let go of me! Let me go!
I guess this is what you wanted.
Hey, Kang Sang-ung.
What are you doing?
Sang-ung.
Open the doors. What are you doing?
I wasn't late today. Thank God for that.
Wait.
Open the doors. No!
Sang-ung, just open the doors. Hurry.
Sang-ung! You can't!
No, please! Don't go, Sang-ung!
Please don't do this!
Sang-ung, you can't!
Don't go, Sang-ung!
Sang-ung wait!
Please just open the doors!
Sang-ung!
Sang-ung! Sang-ung!
The cash wasn't what gave me strength.
What'd you say?
It was my heart.
And just like that,
I ended up dying.
My cause of death?
Lack of money.
As Beomha Group continues with
the launch of their drug called "Spec-up,"
side effects such as
abnormal behavior and hallucinations
continue to be reported.
Last Tuesday night,
the Gangnam area of Seoul
was thrown into total chaos.
A group of about 50 people
began looting local businesses.
They took the "Spec-up" drug…
…destruction to property and smashed…
…attacking pawnshops and local banks.
Continued surprising side effects…
…has stated
they have completed clinical trials
and received approval
from the Ministry of Food and Drug Safety.
In an official statement,
the company claims
that there is no proven link
between the drug and abnormal behavior.
He got Jo Nathan.
He's dead now.
But the Mundane Vanguard isn't.
What do we do now? What?
Is that it for us?
We saved Min-suk, that's true,
and kept his superpower from being lost.
You serious right now?
"Kept his superpower from being lost"?
The thing is,
if Sang-ung's powers had been stolen,
and he saved Min-suk,
what would've happened next?
The Vanguard would become even stronger.
And we'd have no options left.
But on the other hand,
let's say Min-suk had been killed
if he decided to save his powers.
His heart would be so broken
that he wouldn't fight ever again,
which would also leave us with no options.
Sang-ung's gone.
How could it get worse?
Yeah.
It's as bad as it can get.
But also…
it does give us a hand to play.
Because it couldn't be any worse…
the people who've been silent,
staying dormant…
won't be impartial now.
Mm…
There's something you need to see.
What is it?
ABILITY: ABLE TO TURN BACK TIME
TO ANY CHOSEN MOMENT
NOTE: LEFT THE SOCIETY
DUE TO DIFFERENCES IN VALUES
Get this guy.
Don't be late next time.
I wasn't late today. Thank God for that.
Just open the doors. Hurry. Sang-ung!
You can't! No, please!
Don't go, Sang-ung! Please don't do this!
I wish I could wake up
from this nightmare.
I can't accept
that Sang-ung is really gone.
DON'T BE LATE NEXT TIME
Why are you guys here?
He's gone.
It's all over now.
This isn't the end yet.
I need you to listen to me
because there's something
that only you can do.
Sang-ung is dead…
but he can still be saved.
Are you being serious?
Do you remember that detective?
The one who was after Sang-ung?
Go find him.
TASK FORCE 1
TEAM LEADER HWANG HYEON-SEUNG
That man…
SEOUL POLICE AGENCY
…he has the ability to turn back time.
It's been a while.
What? You're not the only one
trying to go to the past, you know?
Better hurry.
What the hell?
-Let's check out the hallway.
-Close off the doors. Hurry!
Yes, sir!
Did Byeon send you here?
Please, you can help.
Help bring Sang-ung back to me.
Changing the past
doesn't always solve your problems.
It doesn't work like that.
What's meant to happen will happen.
And the result is always worse.
We won't know till we try!
How do you not try every option there is?
There's a chance he'll die anyway.
You'll only put off grieving him.
And you won't save the world.
Seriously? "Save the world." Really?
When Sang-ung has been out there
on his own,
trying to save the world
while we're all doing nothing!
And now that he needs us,
who the hell's gonna save Sang-ung?
At first, I didn't like the, uh,
the work he was doing either.
But still.
But still, if he had to fight,
I wanted him to win.
I know I'm not the only one.
I'm sure you were hoping
he would win too, right?
I can't give up on him now.
I could never give up on Sang-ung.
The least I could do
is save him this time around.
Whoever goes back to intervene,
their life expectancy
gets reduced as a result.
Well, that doesn't matter.
I really need to give him
this month's allowance, so…
You seem so certain.
You two…
perfect for each other.
-Drop your weapons!
-Clear out!
-Get 'em!
-Hold 'em off!
After it's over,
your memory of all this will be erased.
-Stop them!
You'll forget everything, all right?
A complete reset.
Keep in mind
that it's just for one minute.
Look straight ahead and run!
I brought your allowance, okay?
Kang Sang-ung!
Hey. Answer me.
Say something.
Answer me, Sang-ung!
Kang Sang-ung.
Min-suk.
Sang-ung, I swear to God,
if you ever do anything that dangerous
ever again, I will…
I'll actually kill you.
Oh, sweetie, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
What did I miss? How did this happen?
I know for a fact I didn't have any money.
-That's Kang Sang-ung!
-No, just wait.
It's okay.
You guys keep the area closed off.
Go find the commanding officer.
-But what about Kang Sang-ung?
-Just do it! Go!
Hurry! Go! Now!
Yes, sir, I'm on it.
Let's go to the west side.
Yes, ma'am.
Why are you standing there? Go! Hurry!
-Go! Go!
-Everyone else, east side.
Are you feeling okay?
I've been better.
Let's get outta here.
-Right. Let's go.
-Right.
Wait a minute.
I don't think Jo Nathan's dead.
Should it be this difficult to come home?
I get involved to save your life,
just so you can come back here to die.
Hello.
You guys sure do work hard.
I've waited for this moment
for what feels like an eternity.
You have no idea.
Do you have any last words
before saying goodbye?
Speechless?
It's so funny.
I've been waiting an eternity
to experience this moment as well.
End of the line.
Any last words for me?
Nope, guess not.
Father.
Father!
Having a happy household
is like indulging in heaven early.
The more I see under this roof,
I'm afraid that it resembles hell.
I guess things aren't going well.
Oh, but don't worry.
You'll stay breathing
until you handle your debts.
What is it?
Haven't you gone far enough already?
I need to bring Sang-ung in.
After that,
I'll get it all under control.
Are you okay?
This is great.
He moves quickly.
That psychopath.
Did he inject every power there was?
He went on a rampage.
We have unfinished business, Sang-ung.
Where are you?
Come on! Come this way! Hurry!
Lost your mommy, little girl?
Wanna look for her together?
You're so noisy.
Here's your teddy.
I need you to go inside.
I have to teach that guy a lesson.
Hey.
You gotta stop bothering
these innocent people.
I'm the one you want.
Why don't you try fighting me instead?
You're right.
You should've gotten here earlier.
This is incredible.
And you kept it to yourself?
It's not what you think.
I know it seems pretty cool
in the beginning,
but after a while,
it really starts to suck.
A normal life is better in every way.
Take my word for it.
You wanna be normal again?
But I don't think I can live like that.
There is no tomorrow.
He goes down today, no matter what.
Hi, is everyone okay?
It's dangerous,
so promise you'll take cover.
Apologies.
There, there, there, there!
Over there, over there!
Having fun yet?
What about it's fun?
I worked my ass off
so one day I could punch your stupid face.
Tonight, I'm gonna beat
the living shit out of you.
Then take you to the police station.
What? What's going on?
What is that? Huh?
What do we do?
Yo, the lights are back on.
They're back on.
I know what you're feeling.
Those are the side effects.
Let's stop this, all right?
Glad you guys came.
You seem so lonely.
You and your rogue mission vibes.
Hey! Yeah, you!
You need to clean up
all this crap you broke!
Sang-ung, careful!
Run!
Bun-mi.
Do you know what the problem is
with you guys?
You love to meddle.
What the hell?
You're already out of money?
What's wrong?
You said you didn't get
your strength from money.
Where did you say it came from?
Oh, right.
Your heart.
Where's your heart now?
That stupid look on your face.
As if you're special.
Who else will fight the bully
if a hero runs away?
What are you gonna do now?
There's no one around to help you.
You're on your own.
Hey, mister!
You can win. I know it!
You can do it, mister.
Here's some money so you can fight!
-Please beat him for us!
-He's a hero!
Stand up and fight!
Stay strong!
Give him the money!
You can win this!
Don't give up!
We need to throw him cash!
Hurry! Throw it down!
Get up! You got this!
Beat that guy!
Throw him some money! That guy down there!
Come on, get up!
Everybody help him.
He needs money to fight!
You've got this!
-Throw it all down to him!
-Let's throw our money! Throw it!
-You can do this!
-You've got this!
-Don't give up!
-Throw it!
Throw more!
Keep fighting! Get up!
Don't give up!
You got this! Beat him!
Bun-mi, you need to get up.
BUN AND MI
You can do this!
That's the guy we saw on TV.
All right! You've got this! Stay strong!
What are you waiting for? Throw him money!
You're always running late.
And yet, time's on my side.
You really need to cut down.
We gotta start taking care of your health.
Kang Sang-ung!
Don't worry about anyone else.
Just don't lose to that bastard.
-What are you doing? Throw him something.
-Oh, yeah.
Right. Hey, let's help him out!
Sang-ung, you got this!
Careful. Watch your back.
Don't get hurt.
Sticking their noses
where they don't belong.
That's right.
When you're a hero, it's part of the deal.
Get him, Grandpa!
Sang-ung, do it!
Some people say… that money has no soul.
Not true.
I've found
different kinds of money
have their own spirit.
So, in this fight against evil…
…I won.
I cleaned everything up.
You can finish the rest.
The ball's in your court.
Kindly go.
CORRUPT JO WON-DO MUST APOLOGIZE!
Can you comment on
the allegations of creating a slush fund?
Did you donate hundreds
of billions of illegal funds to charity
to clear yourself of the charges?
Is it true you embezzled funds?
Can you disclose the source
of your donations?
Let's go.
…in exchange for donating the funds?
Are you admitting
to manufacturing and distributing drugs?
Oh? New watch.
Oh, yeah? You like it?
It looks good.
What'd you do with the old one?
Can we please get a statement?
The old one? Uh…
I left it in the past.
…cooperate to the best of my abilities.
Are you pleading guilty today?
All the evil people
who tried to ruin my ordinary life,
they got their due too.
Taking advantage of the brief moment
of peace in the world,
the society members
returned to their own lives.
BUN AND MI
Can I get you anything?
You know what?
I want the best bread you've got.
Happy birthday, honey.
BYEON SIN-U
All right. Table five, please.
Come. Let's eat.
Can I get a bottle of soju?
You got it.
You've been drinking almost every day.
You're right.
Here you go.
How many glasses do you need?
-Oh, just one.
-Two glasses.
I have to drink to be like you.
Right, Dad.
Keep the tradition up.
Me?
I was finally able to buy an apartment.
It took a little time because I was busy
fighting bad guys and saving the world,
but Min-suk and I
finally have a place to call home.
This is our new home! Here it is!
-What!
-Wow.
Every heart…
Oh my gosh.
Paying off the balance
turned out to be even harder
than fighting Jo Nathan.
Sang-ung.
Look, this is crazy.
-The sunlight gets in every room.
-Yep, every room.
It's a four-bay layout.
This is nice.
Oh.
I forgot.
You were gonna tell me something earlier.
It was, uh, something that was fun.
Yeah, I was. Uh-huh.
Just a minute.
Here.
What? Doesn't it seem fun?
It really does.
It seems very fun.
NICE TO MEET YOU
CONGRATULATIONS ON BECOMING A DAD!
By the way,
I heard you need 360 million won
to raise a kid.
Sang-ung.
Let's work really hard.
Mm-hmm.
I'm ready for whatever
I am ready to roll…
You know what? It is fun.
Look.
But the question always remains,
at what cost?
Wait. Does it really take
360 million won to raise a kid?
Yeah. That's the number.
I saw it on the news.
I'm going to really focus on saving money.
We're going to have a happy home. Okay?
What do you mean, save?
You can't save. It all goes to childcare.
Really? At least I can make you happy.
That much I can do.
I got this!
We're turning the page
Taking on the world
Feeling the rush, new day begins
Making the most of every day
Every scar and every tear
They made me who I am
For in this brand-new day
There's just nothing left to hide
Forget about yesterday
Never looking back
Forget about me
My yesterday
We're turning the page
Taking on the world
Feeling the rush, new day begins
Making the most of every day
Every scar and every tear
They made me who I am
For in this brand-new day
There's just nothing left to hide
Forget about yesterday
No worries, no more fears
Moving on here and now
Every time, every breath
Living life to the fullest
Never looking back
Forget about me
My yesterday
We're turning the page
Taking on the world
Feeling the rush, new day begins
Making the most of every day
Every scar and every tear
They made me who I am
For in this brand-new day
There's just nothing left to hide
Forget about yesterday
Forget about my yesterday
We're turning the page
Taking on the world
Feeling the rush, new day begins
Making the most of every day
Every scar and every tear
They made me who I am
For in this brand-new day
There's just nothing left to hide
Forget about yesterday
Forget it